(Mrs Cooper:)...I will put you over my knee
right here in this restaurant.
(Leonard:)Please pester her. Please, for me.
(Leonard:)Mrs. Cooper,
what did you think of the sushi?
(Mrs Cooper:)Good. The only thing that would have
made it better, if it was cooked.
(Mrs Cooper:)And if it was beef.
(Mrs Cooper:)Sheldon, when is your landlord
gonna fix the elevator?
(Sheldon:)I don't know.
(Sheldon:)Lately, we've been talking
about converting it into a missile silo.
(Leonard:)Your son seems to think we need to
Iaunch a preemptive strike on Burbank.
(Sheldon:)Get them before they get us.
(Raj(Sitting against their front door, drinking a beer):)Hey, look who decided to show up.
(Leonard:)Raj, what are you doing?
Well, I couldn't find you guys
so I bought six new friends.
(Raj:)Three, sadly, are dead.